Finding Aid for the Kelly Miller Smith Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- PAMPHLETS, BROCHURES, FLYERS, MAGAZINES
  - Bienvenu, Sr. Parents and Teenagers, by Margaret Hill (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Preparing Tomorrow's Parents, by Elizabeth Ogg (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Public Affairs Pamphlets - - R-V (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - The Rehabilitation Counselor, by Elizabeth Ogg (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - The Rights of Teenagers as Patients, by Theodore Irwin (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Sensitivity Training and Encounter Groups, by Elizabeth Ogg (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Talking It Over Before Marriage, by Millard J. Bienvenu, Sr. (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Talking to Preteenagers About Sex, by Sadie Hofstein (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - To Combat Child Abuse and Neglect, by Theodore Irwin (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Unlocking Human Resources: A Career in Social Work, by Patricia W. Soyka (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - VD: Epidemic Among Teenagers, by Jules Saltman (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs Pamphlets - - W-Y (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - What About Marijuana? by Jules Saltman (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - What to Expect from School Counselors, by Margaret Hill (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Woman's Changing Place: A Look at Sexism, by Nancy Doyle (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Women's Rights: Unfinished Business, by Eleanor Flexner (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - You and Your Alcoholic Parent, by Edith Lynn Harnik (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Race and the Eighties, by Paul Cox, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Reading is Fundamental: Action for Change (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Reaganomics (Full Employment Action Council) (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Religion at Furman (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Religion in American Life Flyers: (Box 101, Folder 3)
    The Art of Worship
    The Gift That Takes a Lifetime to Make...
    Something to Remember, by Carlos P. Romulo
    Thanks: Giving, Living
  - Rescue News (Newsletter of Nashville Union Mission), July 1977, September 1981, February 1982 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Resources for the Black Church (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Restoration (Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation), Spring 1983 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Rethinking Human Rights (Emory University Symposium), 1982-1983 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - SALT 72 (1972 Christian Life Seminar Proceedings) (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - The Schomburg Collection (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill No. 1248 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Senior Sentinel, February 1982 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - The Sentry (Official Handbook, Mount Zion Baptist Church, Nashville) (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Shawplan (Catalog of Shaw University), 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Singing Children of the Church for Junior Choir, by Rob Roy Peery (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Smoke Signals (Bacon College), Spring 1984 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Smoke Signals (Middle Tennessee Council, Boy Scouts of America) (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - So You Tried It Before... (Christian Workers Association, Trevecca Nazarene College) (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Social Action Newsletter (Department of Church in Society, Disciples of Christ), Spring 1980 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Sojourners (Fannie Lou Hamer, Prophet of Freedom), December 1982 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Something of a Faith: A Brief History of Mary Holmes Junior College, by Helen E. Pfeifer, 1967 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - South Today: A Digest of Southern Affairs, September 1972, November 1972 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Southern Africa Media Center (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Southern Patriot (Southern Conference Education Fund) (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Southern Society of Anatomists Program, October 26-29, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - St. James Academy for Parish Clergy, Summer 1974 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Studies in Jeremiah (Continuing Theological Education Mini-Conference, The Southern Baptist Theological Seminary), October 1981 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - A Study of Black Self-Help, by Willia L. Pollard Summer Science Program Report, 1983-1984 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Revival! By Eleanor Dickinson and Barbara Benziger (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Riverside Church Disarmament Program, 1981 Resource List (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Target (East African Venture Company, Publisher), November 1971 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Task Force on Urban Problems, Reading and Advisory Committee Report, December 15, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - The Tower (Austin Peay State University English Department), 1970 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - A Time for Action: A Handbook for Establishing State and Local Human (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Relations Machinery Timmy's Books about Church, by Larraine Wells (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - To Set at Liberty... (Virginia Union University School of Theology Catalog), 1976-1978 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - The Unchurched American (The Princeton Religion Research Center), 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - United We Build. (Mount Zion Baptist Church) (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Voice of the Plant-tation (General Motors Revolutionary Union Movement), September 1971 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Want to Help: It Won't Cost a Cent (Operation Green Power) (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Washington Memo (Planned Parenthood), 1981 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Where Does the Butterfly Go When It Rains?, by May Garelick (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - White Rock Baptist Church (Proposed Human Relations Institute) (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Who Is the Good News in Your Life? (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - WHY (National Committee to Abolish the Un-American Activities Committee) (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Within Our Reach (Report of the Commission on Goals for Higher Education in the South) (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Witness-Give-Go (America for Christ Offerings), February 27, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Wonderful Saviour: An Easter Service for the Church School The Workers Defense League, 1936-1963 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - World Parish (international Organ of the World Methodist Council), September 1980 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Your Church, 1963, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Zion Baptist Church Directory (Cincinnati, Ohio) (Box 102, Folder 6)
- OUTGOING/INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE
  - May 1, 1920 - April 16, 1946 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - February 25, 1948 - August 31, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - March 2, 1953 - October 26, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - May 25, 1958 - August 8, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - June 10, 1960 - March 1962 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - April 28, 1963 - July 3, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - January 25, 1965 - December 10, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - February 22, 1966 - December 11, 1966 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - March 12, 1967 - June 11, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - June 18, 1967 - August 18, 1967 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - March 29, 1968 - May 4, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - August 2, 1970 - July 18, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - November 17, 1972 - June 18, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - March 23, 1973 - November 17, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - March 2, 1975 - June 18, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - September 14, 1976 - October 17, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - January 2, 1977 - October 23, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - January 12, 1978 - November 19, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - March 10, 1979 - December 23, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - File 1 January 13, 1980 - May 20, 1980
  - July 11, 1980 - July 27, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - January 11, 1981 - November 21, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - May 15, 1983 - September 9, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing Correspondence (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - October 7, 1955 - December 18, 1969 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - January 30, 1970 -October 27, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - November 5, 1970 - December 29, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - January 6, 1971 - January 29 1971 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - February 3, 1971 - February 23, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - March 8, 1971 - March 29, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - April 1, 1971 - April 28, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - May 5, 1971 - June 24, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - June 28, 1971 - September 3, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - September 6, 1971 - October 13, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - October 17, 1971 - December 21, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - January 2, 1972 - February 29, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - March 10, 1972 - May 1, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - May 4, 1972 - June 7, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - June 8, 1972 - July 27, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - August 2, 1972 - August 30, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - September 5, 1972 - October 31, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- KELLY MILLER SMITH PAPERS - SERIES II: CORRESPONDENCE
  - Outgoing, November 2, 1972 - April 28, 1977
  - November 2, 1972 - November 21, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - November 22, 1972 - December 22, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - January 2, 1973 - February 14, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - February 21, 1973 - April 6, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - April 13, 1973 - May 18, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - May 21, 1973 - July 26, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - August 1, 1973 - September 25, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - September 28, 1973 - October 16, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - October 17, 1973 - November 26, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - December 3, 1973 - February 27, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - March 6, 1974 - July 24, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - August 12, 1974 - November 21, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - November 22, 1974 - January 14, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - January 16, 1975 - March 31, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - April 8, 1975 - May 26, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - June 4, 1975 - August 27, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - September 15, 1975 - December 11, 1875 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - January 2, 1976 - February 25, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - March 1, 1975 - June 29, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - July 7, 1976 - September 22, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - October 5, 1976 - December 29, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - January 11, 1977 - April 28, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, May 3, 1977 - March 31, 1977
  - May 3, 1977 - June 28, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - July 12, 1977 - October 14, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - October 17, 1977 - October 31, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - November 8, 1977 - January 18, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - January 23, 1978 - February 28, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - March 1, 1978 - April 6, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - April 10, 1978 - May 3, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - May 4, 1978 - May 16, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - May 17, 1978 - July 6, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - July 14, 1978 - September 29, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - September 27, 1978 - November 9, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - November 10, 1978 - January 22, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - January 23, 1979 - March 12, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - March 18, 1979 - May 21, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - June 1, 1979 - June 29, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - July 3, 1979 - August 7, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - August 14, 1979 - September 20, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - October 1, 1979 - October 11, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - October 12, 1979 - October 15, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 19)
  - October 16, 1979 - November 26, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - November 27, 1979 - December 12, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 21)
  - December 13, 1979 - February 21, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 22)
  - February 22, 1980 - March 31, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, April 4, 1980 - December 6, 1983, undated
  - April 4, 1980 - April 21, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - April 25, 1980 - June 9, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - June 13, 1980 - August 28, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - September 2, 1980 - December 1, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - December 2, 1980 - February 19, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - February 23, 1981 - April 24, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - April 27, 1981 - June 22, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - July 7, 1981 - July 17, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - July 20, 1981 - September 24, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - October 5, 1981 - November 20, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - December 4, 1981 - February 19, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - February 23, 1982 - March 31, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - April 6, 1982 - June 28, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - July 15, 1982 - August 31, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - September 1, 1982 - October 14, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - October 18, 1982 - December 16, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - January 5, 1983 - February 28, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - March 23, 1983 - July 29, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - August 1, 1983 - December 6, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Undated (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Abernathy - Fuson
  - Abernathy - Arnon (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Arradondo - Barnes (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Barron - Beisswenger (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Beisswenger (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Beisswenger - Benjamin (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Bentrup - Blakeley (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Blankenship - Boner (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Booker - Brookes (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Brookes - Brown (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Brown - Buckles (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Bull - Campbell (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Carr - Catchings (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Chambers - Cole (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Coleman - Covington (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Cowap - Crawford (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Crenshaw (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Creswell - Cyrus (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Dain - Delius (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Dennis - Dunlap (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Eadie - Eldredge (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - Ellis - Farley (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - Farley - Fauntroy (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - Federspiel - Flannery (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - Ford - Forstman (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - Forstman - Fuson (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - Incoming, Gadsden - Jones, Walter
  - Gadsden - Gibb (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Gibbs - Green (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Green - Gross (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Gulley (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Gulley - Guttman (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Hale - Hall (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Hall (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Hall - Haney (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Haney - Harrelson (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Harrelson (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Harrelson (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Harrelson - Harrison (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Harrod - Hatness (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Heard - Henry (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Heoning - Hicks (Box 109, Folder 15)
  - Higginbotham - Hodges (Box 109, Folder 16)
  - Hodgson (Box 109, Folder 17)
  - Hodgson - Hoover (Box 109, Folder 18)
  - Hoover - Housewright (Box 109, Folder 19)
  - Housewright - Hughes (Box 109, Folder 20)
  - Hull - Jackson (Box 109, Folder 21)
  - Jackson - Johnson (Box 109, Folder 22)
  - Johnson - Jones (Box 109, Folder 23)
  - Jones (Box 109, Folder 24)
  - Incoming, Jones, William - Pudule
  - Jones - Kendig (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Kent - King (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Kingsler - Knight (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Knight - Kuhn (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Lacy - Lawson (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - LeCorn - Levels (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Lillard - Love (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Lowery - McEwen (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - McFague (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - McGerren - March (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Mark - Massey (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Matassarin - Mills (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Mills - Mitchel (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Mobley - Morgan (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Morgan - Muncie (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Murchison - Nichols (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Nightingale - Otey (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Otey - Paris (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Paris (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - Paris - Patton (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Pauker - Petway (Box 110, Folder 21)
  - Phelps - Pudule (Box 110, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Pugh - Ziegler
  - Pugh - Reilly (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Reist - Rogers (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Rollins - Satcher (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Satterwhite - Setzer (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Seymour - Sloan (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Smith, A. - Smith, L. (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Smith, M. - Spivey (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Spivey - Stone (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Stout - Surface (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Swan - Taylor (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Terrell - Thomas (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Thomas - Torbert (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Towner - Townsend (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Treadway - Ullrich (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Unger - Warner (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Washington - Weathers (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Webb - Williams (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - Williams, D. - Williams, J. (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Williams, M. - Williams, W. (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - Williamson - Wormley (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - Wray - Ziegler (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Unidentified
  - Unidentified (Box 112, Folder 1-5)
- WRITINGS
  - Lectures, Speeches and Sermons
  - About the Course, Lecture, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Accent on Youth, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Adam Clayton Powell, Jr., Lecture, undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Address Delivered to the Annual Convocation of the National Conference of Black Churchmen, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - And Now We Come to the End of Passion Week, Sermon, undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Annual Address Delivered to National Conference of Black Churchmen, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Address Delivered During Conference on Black Religious Leadership and the Needs of the Black Community, edited and compiled by Smith (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Black Church Administration, Lecture, March 17, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - The Black Church and Contemporary Social Problems, Lecture, undated (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - The Black Church and Current Family Issues, undated (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - The Black Church and Politics, undated (Box 112, Folder 16)
  - The Black Church and Politics: An Introductory Statement, undated (Box 112, Folder 17)
  - The Black Church and the Education of Blacks, Presented to Seminar on Religion and Society in the Black Experience, 1978 (Box 112, Folder 18)
  - The Black Church Applying the Gospel, undated (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - The Black Church in America, Lectures, February 7, 1972 - April 15, 1980, undated (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - The Black Church in the U.S.A., Lecture, November 25, 1975 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - Black Church Studies at Vanderbilt, undated (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - The Black Church: What and Why?, undated (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - The Black Churches: A Surrogate World, undated (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - The Black Pastor, Initial Lecture Delivered, January 13, 1977 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - The Black Pastor as Community Strategist, Lecture, March, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - The Black Pastor in the USA, Lectures, September 15 - November 25, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - The Black Pastor Is a Leader, Lecture, undated (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - Black Religion, Lecture, February 1, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - Black Religion in Nashville, undated (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - The Black Religious Experience, Lectures, September 16, 1970, undated (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - Black Religious Leadership, Lectures, February 4, 1974 - January 19, 1983, undated (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - The Challenge of the New Right, undated (Box 112, Folder 33)
  - Chautauqua Sermons, 1972, marked (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Inquiry Into the Night, August 20, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - The Story of Jesus, August 20, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - The Search, August 21, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - On Being Better than the Rest, August 22, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Prop me on Every Learning Side, August 23, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Every Day Will be Sunday, August 24, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Time in Winding Up, August 25, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - The Church and the Black Community, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - The Church and Christian Personality, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Civil Law and the Moral Obedience of Martin Luther King, Jr., Lecture, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Communion Meditation, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Contemporary Black Religion Leadership, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Critique of a Sermon: Needed - A Secure Society, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Critique of a Sermon: The Voice of a Prophet, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - The Current Racial Crisis, Lecture, October 7, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Dare We Thank God for the Church Today?, Speech, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Ecumenical Witness, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - The Eschatology of the Nation of Islam Reflects the Social History of the Black Man in America, undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Ever Day Will Be Sunday, undated (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Faith for the Future, Article, September 1982 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Fragments (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - From Dream to Reality, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - The Future of Theological Education, undated (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - The Haddox Situation, Lecture, February 11, 1974 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Herman Norton, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Howard Thurman's Legacy to Progressive Religious Thought, undated (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - I Question This Argument: If God Is Love, Sermon, undated (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - The Implications of Jonestown for the Black Church, Speech, undated (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Implications of the Liberating Gospel for Us and Others in a World of Radical Social Change: Individual Conversions or Institutional Social Change, undated (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Inquiry in the night (A Christmas Sermon), undated (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Joy with an Action Agenda, undated (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Legacy of Power, undated (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - The Liberating Gospel and the Executive Practices of American Christian Communities: Problems and Challenges for Western Missionary Enterprise, undated (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - Logical Patterns (Based on Baird), Lecture, December 16, undated (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - A Message to the Churches from Oakland, undated (Box 113, Folder 28)
  - Microphones Messages, Nine Radio Sermons, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - The Minister in the Inner City Parish, undated (Box 113, Folder 30)
  - Ministers Addressing the Issues of the Eighties: A Challenge for Social Responsibility, undated (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - Ministry in the 70s, undated (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - Music in the Church, undated (Box 113, Folder 33)
  - No More Twain, 1981 (Box 113, Folder 34)
  - Office of Black Church Relations, undated (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - On Merging the Careers, undated (Box 113, Folder 36)
  - Organizing the Church for Christian Education, undated (Box 113, Folder 37)
  - Our Task as a Black Church, undated (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - Papers and Comments, Racism, Racists and Theological Education, edited and compiled by Kelly Miller Smith, undated (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - The Pastor as Prophet, undated (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - Preaching and Social Crisis, Lectures, October 7, 1968 - March 17, 1982, undated (Box 113, Folder 41)
  - Preaching and Social Crisis: An Overview, undated (Box 113, Folder 42)
  - Preaching and Social Crisis — Purview, Lecture, undated (Box 113, Folder 43)
  - Preaching in the Black Church, Lecture, October 14, 1981 (Box 113, Folder 44)
  - Preaching of Thurman, undated (Box 113, Folder 45)
  - Problems and Challenges for the Western Missionary Enterprise, undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - The Prophet in Ebony, undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Public Policies Toward Racial Minorities, Lecture, 1969 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Puritanism and the Negro, undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Purview, undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Reflections on an Unfulfilled Promise, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - The Relevance of Structure or Structure for Crisis Proclamation, undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Religion and Society in the Black Experience, Lecture, September 21, 1978 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Religion as a Force in Black America, undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - The Religious Thought of Howard Thurman, Lectures, January 22 - April 20, 1981, undated (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Remarks Made by Kelly Miller Smith Upon Receiving a Human Relations Award from the National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Salute to the Black Educational Leadership (Honoring Walter Strother Davis), 1977 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Secret of Power, undated (Box 114, Folder 13)